褐丘小学
孩子们 为了纪念退伍军人节
Now, kids, in honor of Veterans Day,
每年十月份的第四个星期一
我们有请到了一位特邀发言人
We've got a very special guest speaker.
一位我们身边的战争英雄
A real, live war hero:
Woody Johnson
Woody Johnson.
嗨 孩子们 她没骗人 我就是战争英雄
Hi, kids, she's right. I am a war hero.
我爸爸是消防员
My dad's a fireman.
你爸真娘炮
Your dad is a pussy.
当你们老爸忙着抽他们的大麻 洗他们的弱逼
While your fathers were all smoking doobies and washing out their vaginas,
老子可在为你们的自由战屎沙场呢
I was in the shit fighting for your freedom...
当然除了带着丁丁·侯赛因去玩伊拉克婊子以外
When I wasn't giving Iraqi whores my Veiny Hussein-y.
您能直接跳到为什么获得奖章那部分吗?
Can you skip to the part where you got your medal?
这就说到了 婊子
I'm getting to that, bitch.
我所在的精英特种兵小队名叫"红骷髅"
I was in an elite special ops unit called the Red Skulls.
一天我们正在执行巡逻任务
One day when we were on patrol,
我的队友 列兵Jackubowski 中弹受伤
a fellow soldier, Private Jackubowski, got wounded.
我救了他一命
I saved his life.
我拖着那半死不活的混蛋一路跑了三英里的战事沙漠
I dragged that half-dead bastard over three miles of war-torn desert.
实在是英勇可嘉
It was a truly brave act.
这位士兵是怎么受伤的?
How did the soldier get hurt?
你咋回事 诉讼代理嘛?
What are you, the [bleep] hague?
时间过去这么久了
It was a long time ago.
我上哪儿能记住那么多细节?!
Like I can remember all the details.
现在我们就是一辈子的结拜兄弟了
Now we are blood brothers for life.
要一直做彼此的天使
We'll always have each others' backs.
红骷髅 肝胆相照
Red skulls! Respect and protect!
你机会来了
Oh, there you go.
漫迪字幕组倾情奉献
脆莓公园
♢ 旗木 ♢ 偏执绝非过错
♢ 井脑湿 ♢ 白云苍狗
联合译制 ❤
Steve 你特么逗比哭了
Steve, you're a funny mother [bleep].
乐成这幅屌样 你也是嗑嗨了
You'd have to be high to laugh at that.
我就不能不嗑是吧? 净瞎逼扯
I'm always high, huh? That's messed up.
4:20咯
It's 4:20!
听好了 林警们
All right, rangers.
就说他逗比哭了
I told you he was funny.
Steve 哥帮你起来
Steve, let me help you up.
坏消息 林警们
Bad news, rangers.
今年圣诞节你们拿不到奖金了
You won't be receiving Christmas bonuses this year.
- 我去 - 啥玩意?
- Oh, man. - What?
反正哪年我都没拿到过
I never get one anyway.
谁让你丫同性恋 Connie 叫屈个毛啊
Well, that's because you're a lesbian, Connie! Jeez!
那我们剩下几个人的呢? 指着那钱活命的好吧
What about the rest of us? We were counting on that money.
哎呀 为了修缮公园 我也只能挪用奖金了
Well, I had to use the money to renovate the park.
此处"公园"是指我们的房子
By park, he means our cabin.
别扯了行嘛
This is ridiculous.
你跟Malloy已经住豪邸了
You and Malloy already live in a mansion
我们可都还窝在破棚子里呢
while we're stuck in run-down shacks.
消停 草民
Silence, peasant.
我是老大 再难的决定我也得拿主意
I'm the boss and I have to make hard decisions,
比如我就得决定房子的侧厅是用樱桃木还是红木地板捏?
like deciding if I wanted cherry or mahogany floors in the new wing of my cabin.
咋地吧
Suck it!
要知道 Woody和我是上等阶层
You see, Woody and I are upper class.
不用高逼格的东西会死的好吧
We can't survive without nice things,
例如这款真熊毛夹克
like this jacket made of real bear fur.
听着 我的心也不是石头做的
Look, I don't have a heart of stone.
我都张罗着办一场庆祝翻新的暖房派对呢
I'm even having a housewarming party to celebrate our renovations,
我... 希望你们都能到场
and I want you all there.
这贱逼
What a dick.
敬我们的老房完成扩建:
Here's to our cabin's new addition:
圣诞节奖金屋
the Christmas bonus room.
只用了奖金1%
To the one percent.
这派对纯属扯淡
This party is a bunch of bullshit.
是啊 Woody有必要整个室内雪景出来么?
Yeah, did Woody really have to spring for indoor snow?
穷逼才玩雪呢 那是可卡因
Snow is for poor people. That's cocaine.
你好哇 雪嗨子
Hello, Frosty the Blow Man.
恶搞动画片《雪孩子Frosty the Snowman》
堕天使大战
Eight ball fight!
爆爽嘿
All right!
Woody 你的老战友们来了
Woody, your war buddies are here.
嘿 蹦跶哥 死瘸子 左撇子
Hey! It's Hoppy, Gimpy, and Lefty.
战场一失利 绰号就来哩 说你们仨多逗乐吧
Isn't it funny how you guys got injuries that matched your nicknames?
话说红骷髅战队就你一个家伙毫发无损 这事儿够诡异
It's odd how you were the only red skull who made it out without a single injury.
看来英雄人物不光比一般人英勇
Well, I guess heroes aren't just braver than normal people,
还更幸运哼
they're also luckier.
可别忘了 我救过Jackubowski
Don't forget, I saved Jackubowski.
敬Jackubowski
To Jackubowski.
红骷髅 肝胆相照
Red skulls! Respect and protect!
你用这玩意打飞机嘛?
Do you jerk off with that thing?
估计跟迅猛龙给人打飞机一个滋味儿
I'll bet it's like getting a hand job from a velociraptor.
美国内政部
那些个猪头 上层个蛋蛋
Those pigs. They don't have class.
他们压根就不懂什么叫"上层"
They don't even know what class is.
我去 废伏特加
Ooh, trash vodka.
你是这儿上班的吗?
Do you work here?
命运多舛 我大学半路辍了 所以是的
Unfortunately, I didn't finish college, so yes.
我现在立刻马上要见Woody Johnson
I need to see head ranger Woody Johnson at once.
干啥?
Why?
因为我是新任内政部秘书长
Because I'm the new Secretary of the Interior.
你老大的老大
I'm your boss' boss.
真不想害他惹上麻烦才怪
Oh, I'd hate to get him into trouble.
上次玩可卡因天使还是小屁孩的时候
I haven't made a coke angel since I was a kid.
我去 Jorge说搞点丑逼妓女过来
Man, Jorge said he was sending over some ugly whores,
真心没开玩笑啊
And he wasn't joking.
不过看你这样 给上两拳问题不大
At least you look like you can take a punch.
行嘞 咱速炮速决 小心可卡因丁丁哆嗦回去...
Well, let's get this over with before the coke dick sets in
搞得咱们两边儿都尴尬
And makes it awkward for both of us.
嘿 Woody 这几个丑逼妓女给你撂哪?
Hey, Woody, where should I put these ugly whores?
慢着 你要不是Jorge的丑妓女
Wait, if you're not one of Jorge's homely hookers,
你特么是谁?
Who the hell are you?
是你老大
She's your boss,
新任内政部秘书长
The new Secretary of the Interior.
咋地吧
Suck it.
能解释一下这儿是什么状况嘛 Johnson先生?
Care to explain what's going on here, Mr. Johnson?
那个... 是恭候您大驾的派对啊
Uh, this is all a party in your honor.
惊喜
Surprise!
嗨一下?
Key bump?
我们来谈一些重要的事务
Let's talk about something important.
咖啡给我放下
Put that coffee down.
你以为我跟你瞎逼闹呢嘛?
Do you think I'm [bleep] with you?
我没跟你瞎逼闹
I am not [bleep] with you.
你也敢叫自己林警? 你个狗娘养的?
You call yourself a ranger, you son of a bitch?
吓尿了
I peed.
你是我这辈子见过林警圈里最烂的一个
You are the sorriest excuse for rangers I've ever seen,
老娘干这行足有十五年了
And I've been in this business for 15 years.
- 敢问大名? - 去你妈的
- What's your name? - [bleep] you.
就叫这个
That's my name.
是韩文名吗?
Is that Korean?
脆莓是全美最操蛋的公园没有之一
Brickleberry is the worst park in the country.
奥斯维辛集中营也特么比这儿好一万倍
Fucking auschwitz would get a better yelp review.
纳粹德国时期建立的劳动营和灭绝营
在这个垃圾堆有所改观之前
I'm here to turn this dump around,
我都会一直坐镇这里
And I'm not leaving until I do.
"改观"绝非一句空话
There are going to be changes.
第一步 药检
Number one: Drug tests.
过去跟这儿干得很开心 我会想你们大家的 拜拜
It's been a pleasure working here. I'm gonna miss all of y'all. Bye-bye.
接下来轮到Woody Johnson了
That brings us to Woody Johnson.
你连在鸡鸡工厂里口爆的活都干不好
You couldn't manage a blow job in a dick factory.
鸡鸡工厂? 是制造鸡鸡的工厂还是用鸡鸡制造成的工厂?
Dick factory? Is that where they make dicks, or is it a factory made out of dicks?
闭嘴 痴呆
Shut up, you idiot!
我真该炒了你这肥逼
I should fire your fat ass.
不要 请再给我一次机会吧
No! Please give me another chance.
我知道这公园很操蛋 但我有改变现状的良方
I know this park sucks, but I'll have a plan to fix everything.
明早第一时间做给你看
First thing in the morning.
好吧 Johnson 但你最好靠谱点
All right, Johnson, but it better be good
不然你吃不了兜着走
Or there'll be hell to pay.
拜咯 去你妈的
Bye, fuck you.
你不能走 这公园可是你的家啊
You can't quit. This park is your home.
只要忍它个两天不碰大麻不就行了
All you have to do is go without weed for a couple of days.
两小时不碰大麻就能要我的命 更别提两天了
I've never gone without weed for two hours, much less two days.
反正我不要失去我最好的朋友
Well, I'm not losing my best friend.
你戒得掉 我会帮你的
You can stop, and I'll help you.
我真心喜欢在这里工作
I do like working here.
你真觉得能帮我戒掉?
You really think you could help me quit?
能有多难嘛
How bad can it be?
又不是让你生孩子
It's not like you're gonna have withdrawals.
看到那孩子没? 我看到了
See the baby? See the baby!
拜托 Steve 就让我来一口
Come on, Steve, just give me one puff.
给你跪舔都行
I'll suck your cock.
你想怎么舔我二弟就怎么舔
You can suck my cock all you want,
但休想抽到半口大麻
But you're not getting any weed.
我得想办法整治公园
I need a plan to fix the park.
想办法整治公园 有了
Plan to fix the park. That's it!
我的巫毒娃娃都上哪去了?
Where the hell are them loompa oompas?
用于施咒于厌恶之人的扎针玩偶
我了个艹 忘了喂她们了
Goddamn it! Forgot to feed them.
你叫个毛线啊?
What are you screaming about?
我想不出整治公园的法子啊
I can't come up with a plan to fix this park.
那秘书长明天肯定会让我卷铺盖走人的
Oh, that secretary is going to fire me tomorrow.
你在林警工会的好吧
Uh, you're in the ranger union.
她无权炒你
She can't fire you.
- 无权? - 无权
- She can't? - No.
如果你要她尊重你 就拿出点骨气
If you want her respect, be a man.
明天到办公室让她明白 谁才是老大
March in there tomorrow and show her who's boss.
是啊 好主意 Malloy
Yeah. Good idea, Malloy.
嘿 "雪嗨子"到哪去了?
Hey, where did Frosty the Blow Man go?
噢 他得回北极去帮圣诞老人了 小兄弟
Oh, uh, he had to go back to the North Pole and help Santa, little buddy.
你吸光他了 是不是?
You snorted him, didn't you?
是 吸光光了 连帽子带脚
Yeah, snorted him. Hat and all.
谁把林警站的雨槽给重新漆了?
Who re-painted the trim on the ranger station?
早上好 大伙们
Good morning, everyone.
Denzel 午餐前你上什么班儿啊?
Denzel, what are you doing at work before lunch?
这是Denzel头一回清醒又不嗨
Denzel is clean and sober for the first time ever.
我为他骄傲
I'm proud of him.
今早我办了不少事呢
I've accomplished so much this morning.
现在我要写封信给Adult Swim频道
Now I'm going to write a letter to Adult Swim.
美国深夜成人动画频道
昨晚开始那台的节目突然变得索然无味了
It abruptly stopped being funny last night.
从头到尾都是一通屁话
It just turned into nonsense.
好了 Johnson 我们听听你有何计划
All right, Johnson, let's hear this plan.
好的 女士
Yes, ma'am.
好了 这就是你
All right, this is you.
我是个阴道枯萎的仇世贱人
I'm a hateful bitch with a dried-up snatch.
天上那玩意是啥?
What's that in the sky?
不 那是Woody的屁眼
Oh no, it's Woody's asshole!
我淹没在屎海了 但这感觉我爱透了
It's covering me in shit, but I love it,
因为我就是个恶心的吃屎贱人
Because I'm such a nasty poop-eating slut.
我满嘴都是屎
It's in my mouth!
好吃 好吃 好好吃
Yum, yum, yummy!
这就是我的计划 你怎么看?
And there's my plan. What do you think?
你吃了豹子胆了 Johnson? 我要...
How dare you, Johnson? I'm gonna--
要咋地? 你炒不掉我 老子入了林警工会了
Gonna what? You can't fire me. I'm in the goddamn ranger union.
根本就没什么林警工会
There's no such thing as a ranger union.
- 啥? - 噢 抱歉
- Huh? - Ooh, sorry.
- 忘了那是我编出来的了 - 什么?
- I forgot I made that up. - What?
你该被千刀万剐下油锅 Johnson
You deserve to be terminated, Johnson.
但我有个更好的主意: 降你的职
But I've got a better idea: A demotion.
抱歉 屌丝林警没权住这里 但我有权住
Sorry, a lowly ranger can't stay in this cabin, but I can.
你们俩找别处去住吧
You two will have to find housing elsewhere.
别处? 别处在何处?
Elsewhere? Elsewhere where?
- 不行 - 别跟我住 - 想都别想
- Not a chance. - Not with me. - No way in hell.
那我们得上哪去住?
Then where are we supposed to stay?
想拉屎的话
Now if you gotta shit,
就拉到报纸上吧 水槽堵住了
Go on the newspaper. The sink's stopped up.
完美爆了
Perfect.
好样的 Woody 这地方烂得堪比凯富酒店
Great job, Woody. This place is almost as bad as a Comfort Inn.
美国连锁汽车酒店
你大爷 Jim 不是跟你说过交电费嘛
Goddamn you, Jim. I told you to pay the light bill.
真希望他们断我们的电 我就不用看你那张天杀的丑脸了
I hope they do shut it off so I won't be able to see your damn ugly face!
我的天
Oh, god.
还不都赖你让我跟秘书长硬碰硬
You're the one who told me to stand up to the secretary.
我是头熊 你听熊的建议就是这下场
I'm a bear. You took advice from a bear.
说的有理 我再不听你的了
Good point. I won't do that again.
- 现在我给你点建议 - 听着呢
- Now I've got some advice for you. - Lay it on me.
从现在开始 她说什么 你就做什么
From now on, you are going to do everything she says,
跪求她把你的活儿还回来
And beg her for your old job back.
我恨你 你这狗杂种
I hate you, you son of a bitch.
我不想再在这垃圾堆里继续过夜了
I can't spend another night in this stump dump.
我们得把自己的地盘夺回来
We've gotta get our place back.
会夺回来的 Malloy 我保证
We will, Malloy. I promise.
现在咱们还是走一步是一步吧
Let's just try to make the best of it.
- 我的天 - 噢耶 爽死我了
- Oh, lord. - Oh, yeah, give it to me.
- 我的天 - 爽死我了 干我 Jim
- Oh, lord. - Oh, yeah, give it to me, Jim.
求求你 求你把我的工作还给我
Please. Please, give me my job back.
昨晚我这棵老木头桩子窝在了他不该窝在的地方
I saw an amputated stump go somewhere it shouldn't of last night.
滚起来 Johnson 你这条懒狗
Get up, Johnson, you slob.
想要官复原职 你得自己挣回来
If you want your old job back, you have to earn it.
先按这单子上的一条条做起吧
Start by doing everything on this list.
这就去做 林警Johnson即刻出发
I'll do it. Ranger Johnson is on it.
♪ 我是快乐树叫蓬蓬 ♪
♪ I'm Sappy the Happy Tree ♪
♪ 脆莓公园呀欢迎你 ♪
♪ Welcome to Brickleberry ♪
快看呐 有免费枫糖浆喝了
Hey, lookie here. Free maple syrup.
不要 不要 不要...
No, no, no...
给我擦到反光 Inez
Make it shine, Inez.
你在做什么 Johnson?
What's going on there, Johnson?
喂食驼鹿 欢迎游客 清洁公厕 控制熊的规模
贱卖会
这是什么情况?
What's all this?
我要把吸麻的东西全部卖了
I'm selling all my weed stuff.
从现在开始 我要规规矩矩做人
From now on, I'm on the straight and narrow.
谢谢你 先生
Thanks, mister.
好吧 当真先生
Okay, Mr. Serious.
看我这招
Check this out.
不好 我的屁股哇
Oh, no! My ass!
屁股着火了
My burning ass!
着火的屁股上扎了碎玻璃啦
Now I've got broken glass in my burning ass!
你为啥还不笑呢?
Why aren't you laughing?
简直不得了 Ethel
Oh, my god, Ethel.
你必须尝尝这些布朗尼蛋糕
You've gotta try some of these brownies.
珍馐美味啊
They're yumsters.
那我必须得尝尝咯
Mmm, don't mind if I do.
味道果然不错
These are great.
你做的吗?
Did you bake them?
不是 我从Denzel贱卖会上搞来的
No, I got them from Denzel's yard sale.
哦 挺好
Oh, okay.
等下 什么?
Wait. What?
我忘记怎么拉屎了
I forgot how to shit.
好啦 秘书长女士 你单子上的事我都办了
Okay, miss secretary, ma'am. I did everything on your list.
我知道的 Johnson
I know, Johnson.
Woody 我非常开心地告诉你新的领导者...
Woody, it gives me great pleasure to tell you the new head ranger
是Denzel Jackson
Is Denzel Jackson.
- 啥? - 不会吧
- What? - No!
棒呆了 谢啦 秘书长
That's awesome. Thank you, Secretary.
搞鸡毛啊? 你让办的事儿我全办了
What the hell? I did everything you asked!
你为毛要毁掉我的生活?
Why are you ruining my life?
因为像你这样的屌丝不配有什么生活
Because a loser like you doesn't deserve a life.
你真以为我会让你官复原职嘛?
You actually thought I was going to give you your job back?
只要有我在 你甭想再当头儿
You'll never be head ranger again on my watch.
- 靠 你这坨臭... - 别发怒 Woody
- Why, you dirty piece of sh-- - Don't lose your temper, Woody.
我们可以成熟应对的
We can handle this like adults.
宰了她没商量
We are going to kill her.
这种建议才像话嘛
Now that's good advice.
嘿 你能帮我们宰掉那个秘书长吗?
Hey, can you kill the secretary for us?
已经搞定啦
Already done.
这特么是个秘书吧 不是那个秘书长
That's a secretary, not the secretary.
甭担心 卡车里还装着15个随你挑呢
Oh, don't worry. I've got like 15 more in the truck.
下周会有好多咖啡没人煮 好多电子表格没人填的
There's going to be a lot of unbrewed coffee and empty spread sheets next week.
没事 我们能熬过这关的
Okay. We can ride this out.
只要冷静就好
We just need to stay calm.
你说得对 熬到明天就没事了
You're right. We'll be fine by tomorrow.
明天?
Tomorrow?
Connie 明天就该药检了呀
Connie. The drug test is tomorrow.
我们得去找点干净的尿液来
We have to find some clean urine.
我这里有个假丁丁
I've got a fake penis.
这特么有毛用啊?
What good will that do us?
就是随便说说
I'm just saying.
Denzel Jackson警长
Head ranger Denzel Jackson.
这话我爱听
I like the sound of that.
人模狗样啊 兄弟
Looking good, buddy.
我觉得咱们该小小庆祝下 你说呢?
I think that this is cause for a little celebration, huh?
Steve 你搞毛啊?
Steve, what the hell, man?
警长只管举行药检 又不接受药检
Head rangers give drug tests, not take them.
所以你嗨也没关系啦
So you can get high again.
我才不想嗨
I don't want to get high,
你们这些败类成天引诱我真是操蛋得很
And it's messed up that you of all people would try to get me to.
你最近有点焦躁呢
It's just you've been a little uptight.
自从你戒了毒好像都变了个人似的
You haven't seemed like yourself since you quit.
这才是我
This is myself.
我不是那个看着你那些蠢把戏傻笑的瘾君子
The pothead who laughed at all your dumb bullshit was not me.
我永远不会再抽了
I'm never smoking again.
Ethel 干净尿搞到手了
Ethel, I've got the clean pee...
完了 我们算是完蛋了
No! Oh, we're finished!
我们可以再想办法的嘛
We can just come up with another plan.
我们还在飞着呢
We're high!
这个办法都花了我们17个小时才想到
It took 17 hours to come up with this plan.
有了 我们去见Jorge
I've got it. We need to go see Jorge.
他无所不能 但我们得赶紧
He can fix anything. But we gotta hurry.
开慢点 Connie
Slow down, Connie!
太快了 你会害死咱俩的
No! You're gonna kill us!
还是的 就像我老爸常说的那样
Well, like my daddy always said,
杀人要效率 全得靠自己
You want to kill somebody right, you gotta kill them yourself.
哪个猪头在我咖啡里放大米?
Who the hell put rice in my coffee?
成了
Yes!
蓖麻毒 你个呆逼 不是"放大米"
Ricin, you idiot. Not "rice in."
二者读音相似
搞快点 Malloy 快剪断刹车线
Hurry up, Malloy. Cut the brakes.
断了
Got it.
好啦 女士 我们下手快 你不会痛苦的
All right, lady, we'll make this quick and painless.
别呀 我最喜欢痛苦了
Don't. I like pain.
- 狗娘... - 你娘...
- Son of a... - You mother--
嘿 你俩 今晚玩情趣
Hey, you two, shit's about to get weird.
快把奶油拿过来
Get the  Cool Whip.
唉 今晚又是不眠夜呀 Malloy
Well, we're in for another rough night, Malloy.
她赢了 认输吧
She won. She beat us.
我们还是找个新地方重新做人吧
We'll just start a new life somewhere else.
我们不会这么轻易认输的 Woody 你可是战争英雄
We're not going out like this, Woody. You are a war hero.
闪人之前 我们应该去她邮箱里拉泡屎
Before we leave, we should shit in her mailbox.
Malloy 你真是足智多谋
Malloy, you are on an advice roll.
你想干啥?
What do you want?
听着 之前引诱你抽麻是我不对 对不起啦
Look, it was wrong to try and get you to smoke. I'm sorry.
我给你带了个谢罪礼物
I brought you a peace offering.
天底下你的至爱
Your favorite thing in the world.
麦香排?
A macrib?
都换季停售了 所以别问我是怎么搞到手的
They're out of season, so don't ask me what I had to do to get it.
给个小提示:
Here's a hint:
关键词有"奶昔大哥"和"撸"
It involved Grimace and a hand job.
20世纪90年代麦当劳宣传主打卡通人物之一 身体为紫色
Steve 我抽麻时才会喜欢这东西
Steve, I only liked those because I was high.
你不想吃?
You don't want it?
我靠 Steve 看你干的好事
Damn it, Steve. Look what you did.
快特么滚犊子 少来烦我
Get the hell out of here and leave me alone.
我就想-就是...
All I want--I just--
看来我抽麻时才会喜欢的东西不止麦香排啊
Well, I guess it's not just the Macrib I only like when I'm high.
- 洋葱圈? - 不是
- Funyuns? - No.
- 塞斯·罗根? - 也不是
- Seth rogen? - No!
著名喜剧演员 出演过《青蜂侠》《菠萝快车》
是你 Steve 我现在不喜欢你了
You, Steve. I don't like you anymore.
Denzel 你的短时记忆可能恢复了
Denzel, you may have gotten your short-term memory back,
但你忘了自己是谁
But you forgot who you were.
请容我失陪
Now if you'll excuse me,
我要去帮"汉堡神偷拳"交换三叶草奶昔了
I have to go fist Hamburglar for a Shamrock shake.
与奶昔大哥同期卡通人物
快点 Woody 我快撑不住你了
Hurry up, Woody. I can't hold you much longer.
再坚持一会儿 横着拉屎有难度好吧
Give me a minute. It's hard to take a horizontal shit.
好了 拉出来了 把小旗子升起来
There, it's out. Put the flag up.
升起邮箱上的小旗代表有新邮件
我擦 快躲
Oh, shit. Hide.
她这是在搞毛?
What the hell is she doing?
我勒个去
Oh, my god.
她对你这么着迷啊
She is obsessed with you.
这样我就懂了
It all makes sense now.
爱之越深 痛之越切
That's why she's been treating me like shit.
太好了 我们可以夺回以前的生活了
This is great. We can have our lives back.
你只要把她上了
You just need to ram her.
搞得爽一点 久一点 深一点
Ram her hard. Ram her long. Ram her deep.
没门 她太恶心了
Ew, no way. She's disgusting.
你们在这儿啊 赶紧回家
There y'all are. Now come on home.
帮我给Beulah穿上情趣内衣
I need you to hose down Beulah.
她兴致上来后滑溜溜的
Her folds get real cheesy after a good screwing.
好吧 我去上她
Okay, I'll ram her.
搞爽 搞久 搞深
Ram her hard, ram her long, ram her deep.
不
Oh, no.
秘书长来了
Here comes the Secretary.
她追上来了
She's catching up with the car.
简直《终结者2》再现
She's like Terminator 2!
该死 我们完蛋了
Oh, crap, we're dead.
正常一点就行 Connie
Just act straight, Connie.
我很正常 我喜欢鸡鸡
I'm straight. I love penis.
啊? 我是来说药检结果的
What? This is about your drug tests.
你们通过了
You passed.
- 通过了? - 怎么可能?
- We did? - How's that possible?
你们昨天刚做完啊 记得吗?
You took it yesterday, remember?
这就对了
That's right.
咱们肯定是嗨得一逼 给忘了
We must have been so high that we forgot.
你刚说啥?
What did you say?
她知道了
She knows!
真受不Steve这个傻缺
I can't stand Steve's silly ass.
他一点也不懂得职业道德
He doesn't know anything about work ethic.
你好啊 Denzel
Hello, Denzel.
你特么是谁?
What the hell are you?
不记得我了吗? 我是你童年时的小伙伴啊
You don't remember me? I'm your childhood friend.
小叶萨瑟兰?
Reefer Sutherland?
对了
That's right.
我是来阻止你失去最好的朋友Steve的
I'm here to stop you from losing your best friend Steve,
因为你暴躁得都有些混球了
because you're all uptight and kind of a dick.
那我怎么做才能挽救我们的友谊?
Well, what can I do to save our friendship?
抽点吧 Denzel 抽点吧
Smoke me, Denzel. Smoke me.
不 我可不抽了
No, I won't do it.
我这辈子才算混出点头目
I'm making something of my life.
那我给你展示一下你不抽之后的生活咯
I'm going to show you what life will be like if you never smoke again.
麻麻变
Abraca-dopey.
看啊 那是我以前的毒贩
Oh, look. That's my old drug dealer.
对不起 我失去了最大的主顾Denzel
I'm sorry. I lost my best client, Denzel.
牢骚仔的手术看来是做不成了
There'll be no operation for Whiny Tim.
但 爹啊
But, dad!
别特么牢骚了
Shut your whiny ass up!
麻麻抽
Hocus smoke-us.
失去了你这个朋友 Steve走向了人生最低谷
Without you as a friend, Steve hit rock bottom.
天啊 Steve成了流浪汉?
Oh, my god. Steve's a homeless bum?
不 他给流浪汉口活
No. He blows homeless bums.
- 现在能做我的朋友了吗? - 闭嘴
- Now will you be my friend? - No.
太操蛋了 但我怎么样了 小叶?
That's terrible. But what happens to me, Reefer?
不飞叶子之后 你成了卓尔不凡的工作狂
Without weed, you were a workaholic overachiever.
成了第一位纯黑人总统
You become the first all-black president.
麻麻走你
Presto-weedo.
真特么爽 太棒了
Hell, yeah! That's awesome!
等等 我怎么瞎了?
Wait a minute. Why am I blind?
青光眼
Glaucoma.
你把"持有大麻"定成了死罪
You made marijuana possession a capital offense.
- 这货谁? - 牢骚仔
- Who's that? - Whiny Tim.
你为什么要毁我的童年?
Why'd you have to ruin my childhood?
这回我要杀了你
Now I have to kill you.
跑啊 我个瞎子总统
Run, blind president me!
Steve 把麦香排给我热了
Steve, warm up that macrib
咪咪上画好眼睛过来
And paint some eyeballs on your titties.
我回来了 贱人
I'm back, bitch!
- 马上就来 伙计 - 闭嘴
- Be right there, buddy. - No.
Johnson 你特么想干啥?
Johnson, what the hell are you doing?
哥知道你的小秘密
I know your secret.
哥看见你供我的爱情小神龛了
I saw your little love shrine to me.
哥带着宝贝来满足你了: Johnson的二弟
I'm here to give you what you want: Johnson's Johnson.
你很聪明啊 Woody
You're a very clever man, Woody.
这正是我想要的
That's exactly what I want.
天 重回上层中产阶级感觉好极了
Man, it is good to be back in the upper middle class.
手柄呢?
Where's my controller?
去死 Woody 去死
我去勒
Holy shit.
在这儿呢
There it is.
变态玩法 哥喜欢
Ooh, kinky. Daddy like.
Woody 你以为你知道了我的秘密
Woody, you think you know my secret.
但你没看到我有一个缺陷
But there's one gaping hole you missed.
这特么啥玩意儿?
What the hell is that?
你不喜欢吗?
You don't like it?
不 就好像有人打翻了一罐番茄意式饺
No. It looks like someone spilled a can of ravioli.
够了 我...
Okay. I--
又像刚参加完馅饼大胃王比赛的象人
It looks like the Elephant Man after a pie-eating contest.
《象人》同名电影中脑袋硕大无比的畸形人
说完没?
You done?
没 还像孟加拉的街头小贩打翻了他的食品摊
No. It looks like a bangladeshi street vendor flipped over his food cart!
够了
Enough.
这都是你的杰作
This is your handiwork.
你特么瞎说什么啊?
What the hell are you talking about?
忘了你的"兄弟"了嘛?
You don't remember your "brother"?
天啊
Oh, my god.
列兵Jackubowski?
Private Jackubowski?
正是 Woody
That's right, Woody.
你把我丢在手雷上 炸掉我命根子之后
After you threw me on that grenade and blew my dick off,
做女人反而会不那么丢脸
It was less humiliating to live as a woman.
唯一阻止了我饮弹自尽的念头就是复仇
The thought of revenge was the only thing that kept me from blowing my brains out.
我等这一刻很久了
I've been waiting a long time for this.
你要杀了我吗?
Are you going to kill me?
这么简单轻松就太便宜你了
That's much too quick and easy.
我要以牙还牙
An eye for an eye.
以鸡还鸡
A dong for a dong.
别碰我命根子 别碰我命根子 别碰我命根子
Not the dong! Not the dong! Not the dong!
这就对了 Woody 工作没得跑了
Yeah, Woody. You get that job back.
我夺走了你的工作
I've taken your job,
你的房子 你的自尊
Your house, your dignity.
现在 我来补上最后一刀
Now it's time for the final piece.
你夺了我的男儿身
You took my manhood.
现在我要夺走你的
Now I'm taking yours.
不
No!
还记得我们纹上这个的时候吗?
Remember the day we got those?
我们是兄弟 Jackubowski 对不起我让你失望了
We were brothers, Jackubowski, and I'm sorry I let you down.
我知道全都是我活该 你就... 就快动手吧
I know I deserve this. Just--just get it over with.
就算再恨你 我也还是个红骷髅战士
As much as I hate you, I'm still a Red Skull.
我发过誓
I took a vow.
肝胆相照
Respect and protect.
你要知道 Jackubowski
You know something, Jackubowski?
就算失去了丁丁和蛋蛋 你照样比我爷们和霸气
Even without your hose and clankers, you're a better man than I am.
千不该万不该对你做那样的事
What I did to you was wrong.
我愿意做任何事来补偿你
I'd do anything to make it up to you.
好啊 自从出了事我一直没过性生活
Well, I haven't had sex since the incident.
等下 你认真的吗?
Wait, you're serious?
你那个都不是正经阴道
That's not even a real vagina.
好吧 感觉还凑合
Okay, it ain't bad.
真高兴咱们的计划奏效了
I'm glad our plan worked.
我不想再谈这事了
I don't want to talk about it.
你们俩怎么了?
What the hell happened to you two?
别问了
Don't ask.
我们这几天过得不怎么样
We've had a rough couple of days.
我们再也不沾毒品了
We're never getting high again.
那是我的叶子水
Oh, there's my weed water.
我反正学到教训了
Well, I've learned a lesson,
那就是与我的同僚肝胆相照
To respect and protect my staff.
你没盖上奶油的盖 混球
You left the top off the  Cool Whip, asshole!
Steve 你特么逗比哭了
Steve, you a funny mother[bleep].